Mess 'em up good, boys!
Clear a path for me, and be quick!
Watch out, you guys!
He's gearing up!
Ice Ball!
Wait, it's a Popsicle!
We got him!
We broke out.
Those vibrations can't
be frozen. Tough luck.
Ice!
Admiral Kuzan!
He's been stabbed!
To thou keep you dead!
No!
Doing fine, thank you.
Go, Icelock! Partison!
Go! I'll fight!
I'm counting on you, son.
I had him. Damn.
Don't stop moving.
We're almost there.
The scaffold is straight ahead, but first
we need to break through these cracks.
Hurry up and die!
You and the rest of
the filthy pirate scum!
I must!
Every time the rain no longer falls.
And I see the sky.
I think back to when I was a child.
Who could only cry.
Blindly chasing after him.
I fell far behind my only thought.
One day I will be stronger.
Marjorie and gratitude.
Fading with the wind.
Am I stronger now than I was before?
Or as weak as back then?
I don't know for sure.
But until I do, my voyage will not end.
No matter what's next, I'm
walking straight ahead.
So let's go, there's nothing
that can stop us now.
Those times are on our side,
we'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall, but we'll
always keep on standing.
There's no way anything
will take what I hope.
The voices inside me push
me to keep surviving.
I'll go on, I'll get through,
no matter what I gotta do.
The fiercest of the ball can pour upon me.
I don't care why in the
world would I turn back.
So let's go, there's
nothing that can stop.
Though time's not on our side,
we'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall, but we'll
always keep on standing.
There's no way anything will take
what I hold dear away from me.
I know the future's there for us to see.
Straw Hat Luffy, I, Momonga, am the
Navy Vice Admiral who will cut you down.
It ends here.
Vice Admiral, the same rank as Grandpa.
Shave.
Move off.
Second year!
You're finished, Drawhead!
Finger Pistol!
Garp, don't you dare forget
whose side you're on.
You're full of courage, aren't you?
But take this word of advice.
If you're simply not strong enough,
no matter how courageous you may be,
you won't even come close to saving him.
Kill Whitebeard!
Keep pushing him back!
Why don't you just give up?
Hey!
That's Ace's brother!
Ace!
Huh.
Well, seems the white beard brand
is losing some of its punch.
Surely you could have done better than
let that youngster lead the attack.
I mean, look at him.
The boy is hardly breathing.
Guess that's partially my fault.
Say, Pops, let's block the beam!
What a devoted crew.
I've spotted him!
Straw boy!
Right over there, Team Bay! Huh?
Who's that?
And where is it coming from?
Just as I suspected.
Didn't I tell you Luffy
was going to be in trouble?
What the?
That face, why is it so gigantic?
I don't know, I think it just does that.
Luffy!
Is he still alive? Say something!
Oh, easy does it! Ah!
Get off!
You are wasting our time! Sorry.
I think this little Fall belongs to you.
Eva, Jinbei, let me go!
Oh, man, let go of my legs!
I'm so close to him! Let go!
Enough.
He's done his fair share of good.
Treat him. No! Get off!
I don't have time for this!
Get away! Let me go!
They're gonna...
I gotta...
Koza needs me! Please!
He's my only brother!
I can't lose him!
I can't!
I'd rather die!
At any cost!
I gotta... I promise...
I will...
I'll save him!
Ate him quick!
He's in bad shape.
Please, Sergeant!
Do everything within
your power to help him.
Luffy, can you hear me?
Stay with us, friend!
He's nothing but a big-mouthed
kid who goes looking for trouble.
Dumb and clumsy. Careless, too.
But I've got a soft
spot for fools like him.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
If you're ready to die,
step up and meet your maker!
Oh no! Not again!
You, you're always sailing
around wreaking havoc.
But here, you're through!
That's what you think I'll be right back
you wait here hold on you're leaving
I must I won't rest until Ace is safe
Stay away from him it's too dangerous
Die!
Damn you!
Move it.
Pops is coming through.
You think yourself brave,
but if you had any pride as swordsman,
you'd know when to admit defeat.
Move!
Insolent wretches.
Luffy, I shall smite every
man that stands between us!
I'm coming, my love.
She's attacking both sides.
Boa Hancock's completely lost it.
Everyone cover your eyes, quickly!
Slave arrows.
Lovely, the corpse
count's still on the rise.
Quit moving around! You're mine!
Am I?
It sure feels like I'm roaming free.
It's not over yet.
Keep on the alert, man.
Those are the new world pirates
that were trapped in the bay.
Sorry for the wait.
Nice about time!
Just great.
We turned away for one
second and this happens.
Uncle is not gonna like this.
We better clean up.
So get ready.
Show no mercy to our enemies.
And it's fine if a few soldiers
get caught up in the crossfire.
Fire Pacifistas.
Hang on, Ace.
I'm coming for you.
He's flying!
What are you winning, Mark?
Shoot him down!
It's going straight through him!
Never mind that!
Just keep shooting!
What's the big idea?
I never gave you orders to start fighting!
We're doomed!
We have to fight Monkey D. Garp!
This can't be good.
The legendary Navy hero!
Life cycle, Garp!
We got this now! They're finished!
He's the best gatekeeper there is!
Oh, man.
Garp.
If you want to reach the scaffold, you're
gonna have to make it through me first!
Stupid brats.